<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:00:43 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FFB</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/ffb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:00:43 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/ffb/</guid>
      <description>Draft Kit Beer Sheets is a tool I found online and everytime I feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten good results off of it and good feed back from people I&amp;rsquo;ve recommneded it to.&#xA;The original creator moved on from the site this year but it was taken over by his team so it should still reliable.&#xA;Usage You can go to their main page and just copy over the settings from your league.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/first/</guid>
      <description>Self hosted blog for Eduardo Figueroa. Subjects include DIY projects, linux, and other tech stuff probably.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/stack/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to StackEdit! This is just a general overview of what I&amp;rsquo;m running. Updated sporadically, only includes things I&amp;rsquo;m actively using or have deployed.&#xA;Networking In Production Unifi UDM Pro 3 APs PoE and non-PoE switches A certain number and variety of cameras Services Self-hosted:&#xA;NGINX Proxy Manager Immich. Photo Backup. Paperless-NGX. Document storage Recipes. Recipes I&amp;rsquo;ve saved. DokuWiki. Personal wiki. MicroBin. &amp;ldquo;paste bin&amp;rdquo; share. FreshRSS. RSS agregator Forgejo. Git repos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:57:05 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://10.0.0.51:1313/post/test/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to StackEdit! Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m your first Markdown file in StackEdit. If you want to learn about StackEdit, you can read me. If you want to play with Markdown, you can edit me. Once you have finished with me, you can create new files by opening the file explorer on the left corner of the navigation bar.&#xA;Files StackEdit stores your files in your browser, which means all your files are automatically saved locally and are accessible offline!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
